

Samson Grice

samsgrice@gmail.com

0615583910

□ British, UK

math Date of birth 09/10/1999

% lamagicx.eu

Computer skills

Python

HTML / CSS / JS

PHP

C

Applied Mathematics

Git

MySQL

Languages

English

Native

French

Fluent

Interests

Unix+Vim

Piano

Rugby

Social networks



in @samson-grice-lamagicx

Samson GRICE

Developer Internship

Conscientious, motivated and curious student.

About me

British student studying a Diplôme d'Ingénieur en Mathématiques Appliquées at Cy Tech (ex EISTI), Pau, France. Studying Mathematics and Computer Science with specialisms in artificial intelligence and procedural graphics. Alongside this I work on multiple web development projects as a web designer and backend developer for professional and local businesses, and teach programming as a Private Tutor, online and in-person.

Education

Masters

Since September 2019 Cy Tech (ex EISTI) Pau

A 3 year course specialising in Maths and Computer Science.

Prepratory Classes

From September 2019 to June 2021 Cy Tech (ex EISTI) Pau

2 years in scientific curriculum in preparation for entrance into Engineering school.

Work experience

Freelance IT & Web Developer

Since May 2021

Private Programming Tutor

Since October 2021

Website Developer

From July 2021 to August 2021 La Terrasse Duras

Helped design and create the restaurant's new website.

Administrative Website Assistant

From September 2018 to January 2019 Venture 42 Duras

Learnt about web hosting and helped to manage and organise directories.

Head Waiter

From July 2021 to August 2021 La Terrasse Duras

Summer job as a waiter.

Assistant Waiter

From July 2020 to August 2020 La Terrasse Duras

Student Summer Job as a waiter.